export const quizData = {
    categories : [
        {
            id: "1",
            categoryName: "Movie Trivia",
            questionList: [
                {
                    question: "What was the name of the first film in the 'Harry Potter' series?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Harry Pottter and the Chamber of Secrets","Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire","Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"],
                    answer: "Harry Potter And The Philosopher's Stone"
                },
                {
                    question: "How many Star Wars movies are there?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["11","13","10"],
                    answer: "12"
                },
                {
                    question: "In which movie did Captain America lift Thor's hammer (mj√∂lnir)?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Captain America: The first Avenger","Avengers","Avengers: Age of Ultron"],
                    answer: "Avengers: Endgame"
                },
                {
                    question: "Which movie was based on Jordan Belfort, the former stockbroker, and a convicted felon?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Pursuit of Happiness","The Social Network","Catch me If you can"],
                    answer: "The Wolf Of Wall Street"
                },
                {
                    question: "In which movie did all the infinity stones first appear in the Marvel cinematic universe?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Avengers","Iron Man 2","Avengers: Infinity War"],
                    answer: "Guardians Of The Galaxy"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            id: "2",
            categoryName: "Cartoons Trivia",
            questionList: [
                {
                    question: "What does the character Popeye famously eat to boost his strength?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Carrot","Potato","Chillies"],
                    answer: "Spinach"
                },
                {
                    question: "Which of these is not a Looney Tunes character?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Elmer Fudd","Tasmanian Devil","Porky Pig"],
                    answer: "Puddy Tat"
                },
                {
                    question: "What vegetable is Warner Bros. character Bugs Bunny often portrayed eating?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Spinach","Potato","Chillies"],
                    answer: "Carrot"
                },
                {
                    question: "In what year was the animated Disney movie Aladdin released?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["1993","1994","1991"],
                    answer: "1992"
                },
                {
                    question: "Which character has made the most appearances in Disney movies and short films?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Mickey Mouse","Mini Mouse","Goofy"],
                    answer: "Donald Duck"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            id: "3",
            categoryName: "Cricket Trivia",
            questionList: [
                {
                    question: "Can batsman hit the ball twice",
                    incorrectOptions: ["It is illegal unless referee allowed before the match","Yes","It is illegal unless otherwise agreed before the match"],
                    answer: "No"
                },
                {
                    question: "How tall is a wicket in cricket",
                    incorrectOptions: ["20 inches","18 inches","33 inches"],
                    answer: "28 inches"
                },
                {
                    question: "Whay is the minimum number of overs that must be bowled in a day in Test Criket?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["80","70","100"],
                    answer: "90"
                },
                {
                    question: "Where is Lord's cricket ground located?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Canberra","Delhi","Cardiff"],
                    answer: "London"
                },
                {
                    question: "Which is the biggest cricket stadium in the world?",
                    incorrectOptions: ["Eden Gardens","Adelaide Oval","Lord's"],
                    answer: "Narendra Modi Stadium"
                }
            ]
        },
    ]
}